[{"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_7.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 4, 5, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/鸟类动物_2组/Left/飞翔的鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-5.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/小麦/小麦_1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 3, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/5_特殊类别-猫/猫_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-5.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 2, 6, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/树苗.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_6.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 3, 4, 5, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/鸟类动物_2组/Left/飞翔的鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_6.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄椒_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/小麦/小麦_1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 2, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/老虎_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-5.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/大象_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-4.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 4, 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_7.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_7.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L3.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/盆栽/盆栽-4.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 2, 4, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/骆驼_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_5.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/黄瓜_1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 2, 4, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/6_特殊类别_蝴蝶/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/河马_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 2, 4, 6, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/土豆.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_7.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 5, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/4-特殊类别-猴子/猴子_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_L1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_2.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_8.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3, 4, 5, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_3.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_R2.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/狐狸_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/牛_R1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/山羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/竹子/竹子_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L2.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 7], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "把动物选出来。", "content": [{"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_6.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_3组/Right/斑马_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小萝卜_1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L3.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/蔬菜/蔬菜（无边框）/小白萝卜.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/鸟类动物/小鸟组合_1组/小鸟_L1.svg"}, {"type": "animal", "src": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_2组/Right/小羊_R1.svg"}, {"type": "plant", "src": "v2/通用/植物/草/草_3.svg"}], "selectType": "animal", "type": "au-animal-classify"}], "answers": [1, 3, 5, 6], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-01"}]